# MICHAEL A. JAESCHKE

638 England Dr | P: (210) 665-6967 | E: Michael.Jaeschke@live.com

## Professional Summary

<u>Skills and Experience</u> – Professional acumen developed over the course of five years in a dynamic hospitality environment. Problem solving complex issues and managing customer experiences.

<u>Technical Knowledge</u> – Course work in Computer Science; working proficiency in Java and C++ languages. Working proficiency in Adobe Photoshop & 3ds Max. Full command of the complete Microsoft Suite of Products.

#### **Education**

# **Northwest Vista College**

A.A.S. Computer Science A.S.S. Fine Arts

# **Brandeis High School**

Texas High School Diploma 2013

### Professional Experience

#### **Lead Food Service Worker**

**Roadrunner Cafe(Aramark corporation)** 

2019 – Present

opened and closed the cafe while supervising a crew around 12 people. would send the closing reports to the managers, Counted out the banks of the cashiers and the final bank. Provided service to customers. Prepared food items for future student consumption. Would do employee coaching on a regular basis.

### Various Departments/Positions

**Eilan Hotel & Spa (Blue Green Vacations)** 

2014 - 2019

Hired as Server Assistant; various reassignments and promotions to include: Server, In-Room-Dining Server, In-Room-Dining Operator, Barback, Line Cook and Prep Cook. Proficiency across all titles – delivered highest quality customer service in accordance with 4-Diamond Restaurant standards. Advanced industry knowledge; describes and sells award-winning food and beverage selections.

**Steward Staff** (concurrent with above)

**Community Bible Church** 

2016-2017

Stage sanctuary and auxiliary event spaces for service with attention to detail, implementing time management and personal discretion under minimal supervision.